SEAN BLOMMAERT

SENIOR DRUPAL DEVELOPER http://www.seanblommaert.nl

SUMMARY

Sean Patrick Blommaert August 3, 1985 Zoetermeer, Netherlands

T: +316 2462 5019

E: info@seanblommaert.nl

An experienced software developer with a passion for Drupal and Open Source. Acquia Certified backend developer, loves working on challenging projects with talented people. Excels as an intermediary between technology and business. Focused on writing high-performance, maintainable, clean and secure code. Motivated problem solver, team lead and mentor. Active Drupal (core) contributor, maintainer of the Media module in Drupal 8 core.

SKILLS

Expertise Drupal development / Team lead / Software architecture / System

integration / Security / Training

Soft skills Analytical / Communicative / Flexible / Result-oriented / Team player

CMS Drupal

PHP / JavaScript / jQuery / SQL / HTML5 / CSS / SASS Programming

REST/SOAP/SAML2/Oauth System integration

Drupal modules Media / Paragraphs / Search API / Facets / Migrate / Group / Webform

Apache / Git / Drush / PHPStorm / JIRA / Apache Solr / Elastic Search / Software

Memcache / Redis / Varnish

Databases MySQL / PostgreSQL / Oracle / Microsoft SQL Server

Mac OS / Ubuntu / Debian / Windows **Operating Systems**

Languages Dutch (native) / English

EXPERIENCE

2017 - present Freelance Drupal Developer

> As a freelance developer I worked on projects in different roles. Mainly as senior backend developer, but also as an architect and frontend developer.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- UFC (ufc.com)
- Erasmus University (eur.nl)
- 24 Kitchen (24kitchen.nl)

2013 - 2017 Senior Software Engineer, Finalist

> Lead developer and Drupal architect for a wide range of projects. Involved in the recruitment/hiring process and training/coaching junior/medior developers.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Utrecht University (uu.nl)
- Maastricht University (maastrichtuniversity.nl)

- Amsterdam Museum (amsterdammuseum.nl)
- Nedap Security (nedapsecurity.com)

2008 - 2013 Drupal Developer, Total Active Media

Responsible for technical design, implementation and maintenance of a wide range of Drupal applications.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Sound and Vision Institute (beeldengeluid.nl)
- ConQuaestor (financeincorporated.nl and conquaestor.nl)
- National Maritime Museum (hetscheepvaartmuseum.nl)
- ROC Midden Nederland (rocmn.nl)

2006 - 2008 Jr. SAP consultant, Nuon ICT

> Responsible for architecture, configuration and maintenance of multiple SAP Enterprise environments.

2004 - 2006 Coldfusion developer, Zappwerk (internship)

University

Involved in the design and implementation of several high profile websites.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Intertoys (intertoys.nl)
- Dutchs Museum Association (museum.nl)
- Utrecht University (uu.nl)
- Cultuurnet Vlaanderen, Flemish government (cultuurnet.be)

EDUCATION

2017	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D8)
2016	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D7)
2014	Acquia Certified Developer (D7)
2007	Technical Consultant SAP Netweaver '04 - SAP Web AS for Oracle, SAP Netherlands
2002 - 2006	Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology, The Hague